infinitiva.com 2009-12-31

# Privacy Policy - Infinitiva, Inc

At Infinitiva Inc. ("Infinitiva", "we", "us", "our"), protecting the privacy and confidentiality of your Personal Information is important. We value your business and the trust you have placed in Infinitiva to provide a safe and secure environment for personally identifiable financial information.

This Privacy Policy explains how we handle and protect information. The Privacy Policy applies only to consumers who are customers or former customers of Infinitiva Inc. and have established relationships with Infitiva Inc. We understand the online privacy and confidentiality of your personal information is important to you and is essential in our business. Whether you are just visiting our website or are a current customer, we strive to safeguard your information.

We collect, retain and use information about you only where we reasonably believe that it will help us administer our business or provide products, services, and other opportunities to you. We collect and retain information about you only for specific business purposes, and we will tell you why we are collecting and retaining it upon your request. We use information to protect and administer your records, accounts, and funds; to comply with certain laws and regulations; to help us design or improve our products and services; and to understand your financial needs and provide you with quality products and superior service.

We also take steps to safeguard customer information. We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with world standards to guard your nonpublic personal information.

Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer configuration and browsing activity when you visit our site. This information includes date and time of visit, domain name, IP address, actions, URLs, visited information received and sent (bytes), cookies, reference domain and operating system. We use this information to make our website as useful as we can for as many users as possible.

Infinitiva uses cookies to store customer preference information on the use of our site and to facilitate access to restricted web pages during a single online session. Session cookies are used to authenticate your login information. We also use cookies to evaluate and track the pages you've visited within our website. We aggregate this data with data on the pages visited by other users to track overall visitor traffic patterns to help us improve the organization of our site and to understand, for example, the effectiveness of our advertising and marketing campaigns. No personally identifiable information is stored on these cookies.

While you are logged on viewing your account information or conducting online transactions with Infinitiva, we recommend that you do not access other websites during your online session. Always exit from your online session with Infinitiva before moving to or accessing other websites and prior to turning off your computer.

This Web site contains links to other sites not affiliated with Infinitiva. Your use of the non-Infinitiva Web sites is subject to the privacy policies of those sites. Infinitiva disclaims all responsibility for the privacy practices of non-Infinitiva Web sites.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the practices of our website, you can contact us [support@infinitiva.com](mailto:support@infinitiva.com)

By using this site you agree to our privacy policy. When the terms are changed, the changes will appear in this document. By using the site after any change in the terms have been posted, you agree to be bound by all of the changes as well.
